Finding Aid for Roy A. Rappaport Papers 1959-1997
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files
  - University of Michigan
    - Department of Anthropology
      - Milford Wolpoff, 1986-1988 (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous, 1970-1994 (Box 16)
    - Blue Ribbon Commission, 1983-1986 (Box 16)
    - Center for Afro-American and African Studies, 1984-1987 (Box 16)
    - College Executive Committee, 1983-1986 (Box 16)
    - Collegiate Institute for Values and Science, 1976-1980 (Box 16)
    - Endowed Research Professorships-L. S. and A. Development Proposal, 1993 (Box 16)
    - Faculty Seminar-"Science and Human Values", 1976 (Box 16)
    - GEO Strike, 1975 (Box 16)
    - Humanities Advisory Committee-NEH Proposal for a National Humanities Institute-"Knowledge and Society", 1974; 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Institute for Environmental Quality, 1971-1972 (Box 17)
    - Institute for the Humanities, 1986-1990 (Box 17)
    - Institute of Public Policy Studies-Local Energy Policy Seminar Regarding Ann Arbor, 1979 (Box 17)
    - Leslie A. White Professorship, 1987 (Box 17)
    - L. S. and A. Magazine, 1988 (Box 17)
    - Medical School-Task Force on Health and Human Values, 1973-1975 (Box 17)
    - Michigan Society of Fellows, 1975-1980; 1984-1988; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Mischa Titiev Library, 1985-1990 (Box 17)
    - Nutrition Research and Education, 1978 (Box 17)
    - Presidential Initiatives Fund, 1987 (Box 17)
    - Radical College, 1970 (Box 17)
    - Research Club, 1979 (Box 17)
    - Science, Technology and Future Societies (STAFS), 1975-1976 (Box 17)
    - Studies in Religion
      - Faculty Seminar, 1990 (Box 17)
      - Program Review, 1989 (Box 17)
      - Miscellaneous, 1974-1994; 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Substance-Free Housing, 1986-1988 (Box 17)
    - Task Force on Alcohol and Other Drugs, 1989-1990; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Undergraduate Initiatives Fund, 1987 (Box 17)
    - University Diversity Program, 1988 (Box 17)
    - University Press Executive Committee, 1988-1991 (Box 17)
    - University Values Seminar, 1975 (Box 17)
    - Urban and Regional Planning, 1975-1979 (Box 17)
    - Value Implications of Low Energy Proposal, 1976-1977 (Box 17)
    - Walgreen Professorship, 1991-1992 (Box 17)
    - Kenneth Wilson Case, 1986 (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984-1994 (Box 17)
  - Wenner Gren, 1979-1990 (Box 17)
  - 11th World Archaeological Congress, 1985-1986 (Box 17)